宇宙中心的矗立着一座塔 保护宇宙防止黑暗力量侵袭
据说某位儿童的灵知之力能摧毁这座塔
黑 暗 塔
来和我们一起玩吧 快来呀
Come and play with us. Come and play.
- 你抓不到我  - 想得美
- Not gonna get me!  - You wish!
- 杰克  - 妈妈 你还好吗？
- Jake.  - Mom, you okay?
刚刚那次地震可真不小
That was a big one.
又做噩梦了？
Bad dreams?
没有
No.
来吧 去吃早饭
Come on. Get breakfast.
今早的地震给上班族带来了不小的麻烦
This morning's quake is causing major problems for commuters.
纽约今早遭遇五点七级地震
The 5.7-magnitude quake hit New York early this morning.
然而太平洋两岸也受到一系列地震袭扰
Yet another in a series of quakes that has rattled both coasts.
东京再次发生地震 再加上上周的柏林地震…
Tokyo was hit again. And with the Berlin quake last week...
问题就来了 是什么引起了这些地震？
Question is: What is causing all these earthquakes?
天哪 现在连体育娱乐频道也在报道地震了
Christ, even ESPN's doing the quakes now.
但目前地震原因尚不清楚
But we still don't know what's causing them.
嗨 我爸妈让我过来看看…
Hey. My folks sent me over to see...
- …你们是不是还活着  - 我们很好 蒂米
- ...if you guys are still alive.  - We're fine, Timmy.
那地震可真够强的
That was pretty intense.
- 是啊  - 你还好吧？
- Yeah.  - You good?
- 还好  - 我们迟会到
- Yeah.  - We're just running a little late.
- 一会见？ - 替我跟你妈妈问个好
- See you later?  - Say hi to your mom for me.
妈妈 劳里跟你问好
Ma, Laurie says hi.
别忘了 你下课后要去见霍奇基斯博士
Don't forget, you have Dr. Hotchkiss after school.
我们找这些心理医生根本就是浪费钱
We're wasting money on all those shrinks.
他已经好些了
He's making progress.
等一下
Wait up!
嘿 你从我的存物柜里拿了那些书吗？
Hey, did you get the books from my locker?
所以你说世界末日什么时候到来呢？
So when's the apocalypse coming?
拜托了 你就把书还给我吧
Come on, man, just give me my book.
- 怎么 你吃的药不管用了？ - 嘿 嘿
- What's wrong, your meds stop working?  - Hey! Hey!
- 把书还给我  - 你先下去
- Give me my book!  - Get off me!
- 下去  - 嘿
- Get off of me.  - Hey!
嘿 够了 钱伯斯
Hey. That is enough, Chambers.
把书还给我
I need my book.
嘿 你得回家冷静冷静
Hey. You need to go home and cool off.
你最近 一直挺忙的啊 杰克
You've been, uh, quite busy, Jake.
你觉得最近的这些地震…
This big tower in the clouds you keep dreaming about...
…与经常在你梦里出现的那个云雾缭绕的高塔有关
...you say these earthquakes we've been having have something to do with it.
发生地震是因为那座塔在遭受袭击
They happen because the Tower is under attack.
你是个聪明孩子 杰克
You're a smart kid, Jake.
你要明白当你无法…
You know when you can't differentiate...
- …区分梦境与现实的时候…  - 那不是梦
- ...between dreams and reality...  - It's not a dream.
好吗？我不是疯子
Okay? I'm not crazy.
我一直看到同样的事物
I always see the same thing.
黑暗塔 黑衣人 还有穿着蒙面的怪人
The Tower, the Man in Black, the creepy guys with the fake skins.
如果那座塔被摧毁了会怎样？
What if the Tower were destroyed?
世界会陷入无尽的黑暗和烈火之中
Darkness and fire.
我们来谈谈你的父亲
Let's talk about your dad.
又谈这个
Surprise.
你失去了父亲 你的世界崩塌了
When you lost your father, your world fell apart.
你之所以出现末日迫近的幻觉…
You have these visions of impending hell on Earth...
…正是因为这恰恰是你内心的感受
...because that's how you feel inside.
即便是“黑暗”和“烈火”这些字眼…
Even words like "darkness" and "fire"...
…杰克啊 你也是在描述你父亲牺牲的那晚
...Jake, you're describing the night your father died.
肯定没这么简单
Can't just be about that.
杰克 那只是梦而已
They're just dreams, Jake.
不是真的
They're not real.
一定要小心
Watch out.
他们会把你抓走
They'll take you.
他们专抓像你这样的孩子
They steal kids like you.
快到路对面去
Cross them over.
你们与众不同
Special ones.
他们想控制你们的头脑
The power of your mind, that's what they want.
杰克 你没事吧？
Jake. What's up?
今天诸事不顺么？
Bad day?
是
Yeah.
走吧
Let's go.
- 想一块出去玩吗？ - 好啊
- Want to hang out?  - Yeah.
…控制 他状况很不稳定 我们就接受提议吧
...control, he's unstable. We need to take the offer.
- 这是免费接受高水平治疗的好机会  - 这不是钱的问题
- It's great treatment for no money.  - It's not about the money.
- 我在你房间里等着  - 我们现在…
- I'll wait in your room.  - There's nothing more...
- …已经帮不了他了  - 天哪 朗
- ...we can do for him now.  - Jesus, Lon!
你至少得装出一副把他当作亲生儿子的样子吧？
Can you at least pretend like he's your own kid?
抱歉 宝贝 我们… 我们没听到你进来
I'm sorry, baby, we...  We didn't hear you come in.
今天在学校 到底是怎么回事？
What the hell happened in school today?
你答应过我 不去惹事的
You promised me you're gonna stay out of trouble.
对不起 妈妈
Sorry, Mom.
亲爱的 嗯…
Honey, um...
…州北有一个诊所联系了你们学校
...the school's been approached by a clinic upstate.
他们专门帮助…
They work with kids who...
正处在困难时期的孩子
Who are having a hard time.
这个周末有一个开放参观机会
There's an opening this weekend.
应该是个不错的地方
It's supposed to be a great place.
做的研究都很科学 能做脑部扫描 还有睡眠模式研究
It's science-based: brain scans, sleep patterns.
- 我觉得能…  - 行 好吧
- I think it could...  - Yeah, okay.
伙计 那可就是疯人院啊
Man, psycho camp.
肯定糟透了 哥们
Sucks, dude.
更多的心理医生 只会浪费更多时间
More shrinks. Waste of time.
哥们
Dude.
怎么了？
What?
别再盯着你那些画了
Stop staring at your drawings.
你真是把我吓坏了
You're freaking me out.
你也以为我疯了 是吧？
You think I'm crazy too, don't you?
胡说
Batshit.
…我们之间越来越生疏
...driving us apart.
我只是在请求…
I'm just asking...
我们需要帮助 我们俩都需要
We need help. We both need help.
我们撑不下去了
We are falling apart.
我非常爱他…
I love him so much...
…我不能再看着他这么下去了
...and I just can't stand to see him like this.
他曾经多么无忧无虑
He was such a happy kid.
不要再做梦了
No more dreams.
就只静静地睡一晚
Just one night of sleep.
我的朋友 你不用害怕
You have nothing to be afraid of, my friend.
死亡并不遥远
Death is not far away.
想知道世界另一边都有什么吗？
You want to know what's on the other side?
你能看到吗？
Can you see it?
当然不能
Of course you can't.
因为那里什么都没有
Because nothing is there.
- 天堂地狱的那一套都是谎言  - 你下地狱吧
- It's all a lie.  - Go to hell.
我早去过地狱了 现在燃烧吧
Been there. Now burn.
我们失败了
We lost.
不 枪侠不倒
Not while the Tower still stands.
塔就不倒
Not while you still stand.
别让他进入你的头脑中
Don't let him get into your head.
两位枪侠
Gunslingers.
枪准不在于双手
I do not aim with my hand.
- 违此者…  - 忘祖也
- He who aims with his hand...  - Has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于双眼
I aim with my eye.
枪侠 我在这儿呢
Gunslinger, over here.
枪准不在于双手
I do not shoot with my hand.
违此者 忘祖也
He who shoots with his hand has forgotten the face of his father.
- 枪准在于头脑  - 枪侠
- I shoot with my mind.  - Gunslingers.
枪准不在于所用之枪
I do not kill with my gun.
违此者 忘祖也
He who kills with his gun has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于我的心
I kill with my heart.
停止呼吸
Stop breathing.
不
No.
吸气
Breathe.
用力反抗 不要放弃
Fight it. Fight it!
这招对你从不管用 是吧 罗兰？
It never works on you, does it, Roland?
你这种抗拒我法力的能力…
The power you have to resist my magics...
只是暂时的
Not forever.
你转过身来
Face me!
看着我
Face me.
罗兰 黑暗塔终将倒塌的
The Tower will fall, Roland.
后会有期了 老伙计
Until next time, old friend.
黑衣人匆忙奔过沙漠…
The Man in Black fled across the desert...
…枪侠紧随其后
...and the Gunslinger followed.
该死
Holy shit.
- 嗨  - 这个人 他是某种战士
- Hey.  - This guy, he's some kind of soldier.
被称作枪侠
He's called a Gunslinger.
你再看这个房子 外面挂着一个联邦邮箱
And this house, look, it's got a U.S. mailbox.
- 我觉得这房子就在纽约  - 蒂米 七点了
- I think it's in New York.  - Timmy, it's 7 a.m.
该跟你朋友说再见了
Time to say goodbye.
抱歉 我得走了 稍后跟你联系
Sorry, got to go. Talk to you later.
那家诊所的人来了
The people from the clinic are here.
就现在？
Now?
我不能… 我现在不能走
I can't... I can't go now.
你必须走 杰克
You got to step up, Jake.
即便不是为了你自己 也要为你母亲着想
If you won't do it for yourself, then do it for your mom.
- 其他小孩也是这样吗？ - 这种情况很常见
- It's in other boys?  - It's common in adolescent boys.
他来了
There he is.
杰克 你好
Hi there, Jake.
我是吉尔
I'm Jill.
我是你的主治医师
I'm your intake administration supervisor.
这是我们的司机 托比
This is Toby, our driver.
你好啊 小伙子
How's it going, young man?
你打包好行李了吗？
You pack your things?
你们诊所具体是做什么的？
What exactly do they do at your clinic?
杰克 他们和校方已经合作很久了
Jake, these guys have been working with the school for a long time.
没关系 劳里 我们鼓励孩子提问的
No, that's okay, Laurie. We encourage questions.
这展现出他很精神 很有活力
It shows spirit and vitality.
看起来是一个很健康的小孩子
He's just a healthy growing boy.
我可以和你保证我们所有的测试都是在
I can assure you that all our tests are done in a controlled...
…很友好的环境下进行的
...child-friendly environment.
我们处理过很多类似的情况
We have experience with cases like yours.
比如睡觉惊醒 出现幻觉 痴迷的症状
Night terrors, hallucinations, odd obsessions.
相比标准治疗 我们的治疗其实很温柔
Our approach is actually very gentle compared to standard treatments.
我知道你在担心 其实你一点也不用害怕
I understand your concerns, but you don't have to worry at all.
妈妈 帮我打包一下东西 好么？
Mom, help me pack?
好的
Yeah.
就去两天而已
It's two days.
你要带紧身一点的牛仔裤还是宽松一点的？
Do you want your ripped jeans or your regular ones?
- 怎么了  - 妈妈 是他们
- What's wrong?  - Mom, it's them.
- 是谁？ - 是我梦里的那些人
- What?  - It's the skin people from my dream.
- 宝贝 你不能在想这些了  - 不 妈妈 你听我说
- Honey, you need to stop this.  - No, you have to listen to me.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
他不是人类
He's not human.
- 这不是他真正的面孔  - 天呐
- That's not his real face.  - For chrissake.
闭嘴 朗
Shut up, Lon.
你肯定希望我疯了 这样你就可以赶我走
You actually hope I'm crazy, just so you can get me out of here.
妈妈 你得相信我
Mom, you have to believe me.
- 朗 或许…  - 你没发现他越来越不对劲了吗
- Lon, maybe this...  - Can't you see he's gotten worse?
你现在必须跟他们走
You're gonna go with them right now.
不然 我对天发誓 我就自己动手把你拖下楼去
Or, I swear to God, I will drag you down the stairs myself.
孩子 就去两天
It's one weekend, kiddo.
如果你不喜欢哪里 我就带你回来
If you don't like it, then I'll come get you.
我保证
I promise.
好吧 我去
Okay, I'll go.
- 妈妈 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you, Mom.  - I love you too.
我得去拿我的牙刷
I'm just gonna get my toothbrush.
- 他只是去拿他的东西  - 他想逃跑
- He's just getting his things.  - He's trying to escape.
逃跑？
Escape?
杰克？
Jake?
天呐 杰克？杰克！
Chrissake. Jake? Jake!
杰克！
Jake!
- 杰克！ - 去抓他
- Jake!  - Get him.
- 快回来！ - 别担心
- Come back here!  - Don't worry.
托比会把他安全带回来
Toby will get him down safely.
别跑
Stop running.
- 妈妈 你还好吗？ - 你在哪里
- Mom? You okay?  - Where are you?
杰克 你不能老是这样跑掉
You can't just run away like that, Jake.
- 快回家  - 对不起 我不回去
- Please come home.  - Sorry, I can't.
快点回家
Right now.
杰克？
Jake ?
我过会在打给你
I'll call you later.
爱你 妈妈
Love you, Mom.
你好 旅行者
Greetings, traveler.
请输入目的地
Please enter destination.
一 九
One, nine.
一 九 一 九 中世界
One, nine, one, nine. Mid-World.
中世界 目的地通道
Mid-World. One-way destination.
放我出去！
Let me go!
停下！
Stop!
什么鬼？
What?
天呐
Whoa.
好吧…
Okay...
挺好的
This is good.
简直难以置信
It's all real.
新候选人 女性 十一岁
New candidate. Female, age 11.
看起来不错
Looks good.
正在抵达
Arriving!
先生 欢迎回来
Welcome back, sir.
去找个面具吧 鼠人
Find yourself a face, Rat Boy.
你这是在我的地盘上
You're in my house.
旅途愉快吗？
How was your trip?
还好 我们有新目标了吗？
Fine. Do we have any new leads?
有了
Got it.
现在情况如何？
What have you got?
这些都是我们觉得有价值的目标
These are all showing promise.
我们的追踪者正在抓捕他们
Our trackers are going out to them as we speak.
出现了十分严重的…
There's been a serious breach of...
我不喜欢等待
I'm not fantastic at waiting.
长官 有人非法使用通道
Unauthorized crossing, sir.
那是地球上的一条旧通道
One of the old portals on Keystone Earth.
以前出现过这种情况么？
Has that ever happened before?
给我找一个最近的通道入口
Find me a portal close by.
- 我喜欢你的面具  - 长官？
- Love your mask.  - Sir?
一张美丽的脸庞 整个世界都为之沉默
Choose a pretty face and the world is your oyster.
校准中 长官
Aligning, sir.
你是谁？
Who are you?
是你啊
It's you.
我是… 我是杰克
I'm... I'm Jake.
杰克… 杰克·钱伯斯
Jake... Jake Chambers.
我梦到过你
I dreamt about you.
别杀我
Please.
给你
Here.
看
Look.
你是枪侠 是吗？
You're a Gunslinger, right?
这儿已经没有枪侠了 再也不会有了
There are no Gunslingers. Not anymore.
- 但我看到了你啊  - 你梦到的不是真的 孩子
- But I saw you.  - Your dreams deceived you, boy.
你梦到的东西只是你想象中的那样
Told you what you want to hear.
我走了很长的路才找到你
I came a long way to find you.
我来自另一个世界
From another world!
那祝你归途愉快
Have a nice trip back.
嗨 等一下
Hey. Wait!
等一下嘛
Dude, come on.
我看到你了
Look, I saw you.
这里就是战场 你在射击黑衣人 并且…
There was a battlefield, and you were fighting the Man in Black. And there...
黑衣人？
The Man in Black?
- 是 是啊  - 你认识他？
- No, no, no.  - You know him?
- 请冷静一下 好吗  - 他让你来的
- Stop. Please, please, please.  - He sent you.
他又让你来耍什么阴谋诡计
You're one of his tricks.
- 不 不 不 我真的不认识他！ - 他藏在哪里？
- No, no, no. I don't know!  - Where is he hiding?!
- 他藏在哪里？ - 我发誓 我真不知道
- Where is he hiding?!  - I don't know, I swear!
我只…我只是在我的梦里见过他 就像在梦里见过你一样！
I just...I just saw him in my dreams, like I saw you!
你叫罗兰 对吧？
Your name is Roland, right?
求你
Please.
你什么时候见到的？
When did you first see this?
一年前
A year ago.
- 他是谁？ - 他是一个巫师
- Who is he?  - He's a sorcerer.
在你所看到的那些幻象中 沃特也在这里？
In all your visions, Walter is here?
- 呃，是  - 就在这里？
- Uh, yeah.  - In this place?
是的
Yeah.
等一下 他叫沃特？
Wait, his name's Walter?
酷极了 那个送你了
Cool. Yeah, keep it.
我一定会找到你的
I will find you.
那边的森林里有一个村落 我们就去那里吧
There's a tribe beyond that forest. We'll go there.
那里的预言家可以读到你看到的东西
They have seers who will read your visions.
走吧 快跟上…
Let's go. Keep Up...
好吧…
Okay...
…我从滑梯上滑下来
...I went down the slide.
接着我洗了我的鼻子 再去滑滑梯
Then I got water up my nose, and I went down...
- …我什么都看不到  - 仇恨
- ...and I couldn't see anything.  - Hate.
好吧
Yeah.
宝贝 怎么了？
Sweetheart? What's wrong?
沃特·帕蒂可 您怎么大驾光临了？
Walter Padick. To what do we owe this great honor?
在你的城市里 有人未经过你的允许
Someone used a portal here, in your city...
…使用了通道
...without your knowledge.
还杀掉了守护恶魔
Killed the house demon.
不好意思 先生
Forgive me, sire.
我们会找到他的
We'll find out who this trespasser is and where he went.
已经在找了
Already on it.
试试看这个
Now be a good dog.
这是人类的血
The blood is human.
小男孩…
BOY...
他的灵力很纯洁
His Shine is pure.
所以他才能进入通道
So that's how he got through.
先生？
Sir?
守护恶魔是非常可怕的生物…
House demons are formidable beings...
但是灵力强大的人能制服它们
...but a truly powerful psychic could override it.
这男孩灵力强大到可以杀死一个恶魔？
A boy with the Shine strong enough to kill a demon?
我们这是中头彩了啊
Jackpot
塞尔 两个蒙面人昨天都没搞定一个男孩？
Sayre, didn't two skins have trouble with a kid yesterday?
别吃这个
Don't eat that.
我可不想剩下的路都背着你走
Don't want to have to carry you for the rest of the way.
罗兰
Roland?
他们是什么
What are they?
蒙面人
Taheen.
沃尔特的部下
They belong to Walter.
不要在树林里走 不安全
Don't run off in the woods. It's not safe.
但是刚刚你不是走进树林了嘛
But you were the one who ran off.
因为你说你饿了
You said you were hungry.
好吧
What?
以前这里是个游乐园
You had theme parks here.
这些都是史前的建筑了
These ancient structures are from before the world moved on.
没有人知道它们是什么
No one knows what they are.
他们是主题公园
They're theme parks.
我看到你和他作战
I saw you fight him.
遍地尸体
There was a field covered with bodies.
那是我们的决战
That was our final stand.
那天我的父亲牺牲了
I lost my father that day.
你都看到了？
You saw that?
那场战争
Was it about the Tower?
是不是关于黑暗塔的
The war?
是的
Yes.
继续吃你的兔肉吧
Now, eat your rabbit.
很荣幸见到你 先生
It's an honor to meet you in person, sir.
请问您来这有什么事么？
What brings you here?
有什么可以效劳的？
How may we serve him?
我听说你们没抓住那个孩子
Well, I hear you lost a kid.
这不是我们的错
It... It wasn't our fault.
那个小孩仿佛知道我们的真实身份 我们正在竭尽全力…
It was as if the child knew what we were.We're doing everything we can...
- 告诉我他的名字和位置  - 都在这儿呢
- Name and location.  - It's all in here.
杰克·钱伯斯
"Jake Chambers."
现在
Now kill...
相互厮杀
...each other.
别紧张 好好欣赏吧 各位
Calm down. Enjoy the show, folks.
好戏还在后头呢
You ain't seen nothing yet.
你画的挺不错啊
You draw with a good hand.
我都不知道自己画的是什么
I don't know what this is.
这是幅地图
It's a map.
我父亲曾经给我看过这样的地图
My father showed me a...A map like this once.
在圈子之内 是你我的世界
Inside the circle is your world and my world...
还有更多的世界
...many others.
没人知道具体有多少世界
No one knows how many.
黑暗塔矗立在万物的中央
The Dark Tower stands at the center of all things.
自万物之始 矗立于此
And it's stood there from the beginning of time.
它可以发出强大的能量
And it sends out powerful energy...
这能量保护了宇宙
...that protects the universe...
把我们和外界隔绝开来
...shields us from what's outside.
你说的“外界”是什么意思
What do you mean, "outside"?
宇宙之外有什么？
What's outside the universe?
宇宙之外是一片无尽的黑暗
Outside is endless darkness...
充满了试图接近我们的恶魔
...full of demons trying to get to us.
沃尔特想摧毁黑暗塔 放出恶魔
Walter wants to tear down the Tower and let them in.
如果黑暗塔倾塌 他将主宰全宇宙
When the Tower falls, he'll rule...
怪物将四处横行
...in a world full of monsters.
你是不是要阻止他们
But you're trying to stop him, aren't you?
你在保护黑暗塔
To protect the Tower.
我看到他们试图摧毁黑暗塔
I've seen them try to destroy it.
- 如果我们到达那里…  - 杰克 这只是你的一厢情愿罢了
- If we could just get there...  - There is no "we," Jake.
我一心只想找到
All that matters to me is that I find...
并杀死沃尔特
...and kill Walter.
仅此而已
That's it.
光束震动
Beamquake.
很强烈
Strong.
听起来像是有人在尖叫
Sounds like screams.
这和我老家的几次地震情况相似啊
They're just like the quakes we get back home.
是的 一个世界发生的事
Yeah, what happens in one world...
会影响到其它的世界
...echoes in others.
希望我妈妈没事
Hope my mom's okay.
去睡一会儿吧
Try to get some sleep.
我睡不着
That's not happening.
杰克
Jake.
嘿 我的孩子
Hey, kiddo.
你在哪？
Where are you?
与你同行的人都会死
Everyone who walks with you dies.
杰克
Jake.
嘿 我的孩子
Hey, kiddo.
爸爸？
Dad?
好久不见了
Long time.
很高兴见到你 你长高了
It's good to see you, man. You got tall.
这不是真的
This isn't real.
- 你不是…  - 我还没死呢
- You're...  - Dead?
在这个世界里 我还没死
Not here.
我好想你
I missed you.
我也很想你 我的孩子
I missed you too, kiddo.
过来
Come on.
别害怕
It's okay.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
不
No.
黑暗和烈火
Darkness and fire.
杰克！
Jake!
离它远点！
Get away from it!
罗兰 我的儿子
Roland. My son.
跟我来
Come with me.
没事了
It's okay.
它走了
It's gone.
刚才那个是我的爸爸
My dad was in there.
不 他们感知到你的弱点
No, they sense your weakness...
用幻觉来分散你的注意力
...create illusions to distract you.
那不是你所认识的人 杰克
That wasn't anybody you know.
我能体谅你的心情
I'm sorry.
那只是一个小的时空裂缝
That was just a small tear.
每次塔遭受攻击后都会出现这样的裂缝
They happen after every attack on the Tower.
要是黑暗塔被摧毁了 是不是那些怪物就要来了
Those things, they're what's coming if the Tower falls, aren't they?
是的
Yes.
那如果我们找到了那些孩子所在的位置 我们…
But if we find that place where they're keeping the kids, we could...
- 嘘嘘嘘嘘  - 怎么了？
- Shh, shh, shh.  - What?
附近有动静
Something got out.
快跑！杰克 快跑！
Run! Jake, run!
你需要帮助
You're gonna need help.
我还受过更重的伤呢
I've hurt worse.
可是你在流血
But you're bleeding.
我恢复的很快
I heal fast.
你刚才表现不错
You handled yourself well.
敢去拿那把枪 很勇敢
That was brave, going for the gun.
警方会找到他的 劳丽
They're gonna find him, Laurie.
我们填了一大堆表格 提供了他的照片
We filled out every form. They have his picture.
希望你们不要介意 我把这里当做自己家
I hope you don't mind me making myself at home.
我们那里没有鸡肉
Where I come from,we don't have chicken.
- 你到底是谁？ - 朗 你知道的
- Who the hell are you?  - Oh, you know me, Lon.
是你叫我过来的
You're the one that called me here.
不是说你是打电话叫我来的
Not by the telephone...
而是我感觉到了你那强烈的愿望 你想甩掉那个小家伙
...but with your every desire to get rid of the brat...
这样的话你就可以得到他妈妈更多的爱
...all in the hopes that Mommy there might love you best.
你这懦夫 朗
But you'll always be a seat-filler, Lon.
- 你快点滚出去  - 朗
- You get out of here right now.  - Lon.
这是出现在杰克画作里的那个男人
It's the man from Jake's drawings.
画作？
Drawings?
停止呼吸
Stop breathing.
- 啊！ - 安静
- Aah!  - Quiet.
画作
Drawings.
带我去看看
Show me.
好吧 看起来这小家伙像是成天在跟踪我啊
Well, it looks like I've got myself a stalker.
枪侠
Gunslinger.
你儿子是不是挺特别的
This son of yours is quite special,isn't he?
你没有相信他
The guilt you must feel...
你肯定会因此感到内疚
...not believing in him.
而且还把你唯一的孩子送到了庇护所
And you sent your only child off to the asylum.
真为你
Shame...
感到羞耻
...on you.
有陌生人来了
Stranger approaching!
去看看
Gather round!
祝天长 夜爽
Long days, pleasant nights.
祝收成加倍
May you have twice that number.
我上次见到地球人的时候 还只是个年轻人
I haven't seen one of your kind since I was a young man.
你这么活生生的…
Seeing you here, alive...
你们这能力最强的预言家是谁
Who's your strongest seer?
那就是我了
That would be me.
我叫艾拉
I'm Arra.
这地方出现在这个男孩的幻象中
The boy here has visions of this place.
我要知道这是什么地方
I need to know where it is.
黑衣人
The Man in Black.
老大 我们已经对塔造成严重损伤了
We managed to do some serious damage, sir...
- 但它还是没有坍塌  - 这不重要了
- ...but it didn't fall.  - None of that matters.
我找到关键人物了 这个孩子会以一己之力
I found the one. This kid's going to bring down the Tower...
摧毁黑暗塔
...all by his lonesome.
- 那个孩子在哪  - 他就在这
- Where is this child?  - He's here...
在中世界
...on Mid-World...
他们在我的一个老朋友 艾德的罗兰
...looking for an old friend of mine, Roland of Eld.
等下 我还以为枪侠都死光了呢
Wait, I thought all the Gunslingers were dead.
罗兰那阻挡我魔法的能力
Roland's always had an annoying ability...
真是令人讨厌
...to resist my magics.
所以我基本把他在乎的人都杀了
So I basically killed everyone he ever cared about.
上次我听说他在 漫无目的的闲逛
Last I heard, he was roaming the Mohaine aimlessly.
- 那个男孩正是要去那里  - 莫因沙漠么 那不是…
- That's where the boy is going.  - Mohaine Desert? Isn't that...?
是的 那是个壮观的沙漠 那男孩的灵力也颇为壮观啊
Vast. Yes. And so is this boy's Shine.
老大 我马上派我们的人过去
I'll send our trackers in the region, sir.
这会恶化的
This will get worse.
我这没办法治疗你受的伤
I don't have anything that can help with that.
你需要休息 让伤口愈合
You need to rest, let it heal.
我没事的
I'll be fine.
谢谢你
Thankee, Sai.
你从地球大老远跑过来找他
You've come all the way from Keystone Earth to find him.
他所具有的灵力超乎寻常
His Shine is beyond anything I've ever seen.
灵力？
Shine?
灵知之力
Psychic powers.
很少有人生来就有这种能力
Very few are born with this gift.
大多数人这方面的能力很弱 都注意不到自己具有这个能力
Often, the power is so slight, people don't even know they have it.
杰克 你的灵力太强了
Your Shine burns so brightly, Jake.
你身上潜力之大 难以想象
You have potential I can't even begin to understand.
哇
Whoa.
她的声音跑进我脑袋里了
Her voice was in my head.
杰克 你天赋异禀
Your gift is extraordinary, Jake.
所以你能看到别的世界
It made you see across worlds.
那些画
The drawing.
你画的画 是怎么回事
What about the drawing?
集中注意
Concentrate.
让我看看你的幻象
Share your visions with me.
放开
Open up.
让我看看
Show me.
黑衣人
The Man in Black...
杰克
Jake.
穿过沙漠
Fled across the desert.
告诉我
Tell me.
他在哪
Where is he?
在废土之地的北部
Northern Wastelands.
到那边至少得要六个月的时间
That's more than six months of travel.
但是有你的帮助 我们能更快到那边
But you can get me there faster than that.
黑衣人和他的手下控制了所有的通道运输
The Man in Black and his men keep track of all portal travel.
- 我得去那边  - 通道是什么
- I need to get there.  - Portals.
就算我们愿意 我们也帮不了你
We couldn't help you, even if we wanted to.
要想去他们的地盘 唯一的办法就是通过他们的基地
The only way to access their territories is from one of their own bases.
那我步行过去好了
Then I'll make it on foot.
等下
Wait.
那些蒙面人…
The fake-skins...
是不是会把其他世界的孩子们抓走
...they take kids from different worlds, right?
我在纽约的时候 他们试图把我抓走
They tried to take me from New York.
- 是不是就是说他们…  - 他们在那边有个基地
- Doesn't that mean that they...?  - They have a base there.
通过那边的通道我们能直接到达画上的这个地方
With a portal that can take me right to this place.
你要把我们送回地球
You're gonna send us to Keystone Earth.
我们正在把能量转移到发电机上
We're diverting power to the generators.
不久后通道就充能完毕了
The portal will be ready shortly.
你的世界里有枪么
Do they have guns in your world?
有啊
Yeah.
那子弹呢 是不是像这边一样稀有
And bullets, are they as rare as they are here?
你肯定会爱上那个地方的 地球上子弹可多了
You're gonna like Earth. A lot.
我们约定过的 除非村庄陷入危险之中 我们绝不启用这个通道
We agreed we'd never use the portal unless the village was in danger.
他们会发现我们 然后到这来
They will find out we have it and come.
我们不能违背枪侠的意志 他的意志即是律法
We can't disobey a Gunslinger. It's the law.
- 你们又何从得知他的真实身份呢  - 艾拉
- How do you know what he is?  - Arra.
你肯定对他用过灵知之力了
You must have read him.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
他是基列地的罗兰
He's Roland of Gilead.
他是艾德的最后一位后裔
Last of the line of Eld.
但是他的灵魂在黑衣人的口袋里
But the Man in Black has his soul in his pocket...
仇恨充斥着他的内心
...and his heart's consumed by vengeance.
他不是枪侠了
He's not a Gunslinger.
不是以前的那个他了
Not anymore.
你有什么想解释的么
Or would you tell us differently?
只有山羊才会对预言家撒谎
Only a goat would lie to a seer.
你让你的祖先背上骂名
You dishonor your ancestors.
枪侠们曾发誓要保卫黑暗塔…
The Gunslingers have sworn an oath to defend the Tower...
看看你周围的世界吧
Look around you.
战争已经结束了 我们输了
The war is over, and we lost.
走出自己的世界 用眼睛看看吧
If you left your little haven, you would see that for yourself.
到处都是黑暗
The darkness is everywhere...
反抗是徒劳无功的
...and trying to fight against it accomplishes nothing.
你们大多数人还没有出生时 我就在为保护黑暗塔而战了
I was fighting to defend the Tower before most of you were even born.
我以前一直
There's always a battle.
为它而战
Always.
但我再也不会了
But no more.
正是因为有你这样的想法 我们才会输
Isn't that why we're losing?
因为所有人都放弃了信仰
Because everyone stopped believing.
只要黑暗仍未消散 黑暗塔终会倾塌
As long as the darkness is out there, the Tower will fall.
在那之前 我要复仇
And before that happens, I will get my revenge.
我觉得
Look.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
尽管他不太喜欢我
And he doesn't even like me that much.
他还是枪侠
He's still a Gunslinger.
我能感觉到的
I know he is.
估计现在差不多准备好了
Should be ready anytime now.
调准位置后 通道应该会通向
As soon as it aligns, it should open...
你的世界中的
...in an unobstructed area in your city...
一片开阔地上
...on your version of Earth.
“应该”？
"Should"?
这项技术已经很老了
Technology's very old.
记住那一串数字 若是要回到这里就要靠它们了
Remember that number. It's your way back here.
明白了
Got it.
我以前用过通道
Been there.
嘿
Hey.
你没事吧
You Okay?
怎么了
What's wrong?
没能量了
We're losing power.
老大 他们进村子了
Sir, they're in the village.
法拉斯 唉
Oh, no. Faras.
- 你能修好它么  - 村子里有备用零件
- Can you fix it?  - We have spare parts in the village.
杰克 去附近找个地方躲起来
Jake, go find somewhere close to hide, understand?
好
Yeah.
快跑！
Come on!
快躲进屋
Get inside!
- 我们快走 快  - 你没事吧
- We need to go! Hurry!  - Are you okay?
去拿武器
Go get weapons!
走哪边
Which way?
就在那边
In there.
他就在那
He's there.
他受伤了
He's hurt.
我的孩子 求求你们了！
My child! Please!
他的枪由亚瑟·艾德本人的
His guns are forged from the steel...
剑重铸而成
...of the sword of Arthur Eld himself.
地球人把它称作“誓约胜利之剑”
I believe Keystoners call it Excalibur.
你们快走吧！
Please, just go!
去找人帮忙吧！
Just get help, please!
- 我们不能待在这了  - 不 我得救他们出来
- We have to get out of here.  - No, I've got to get them out!
别管了 我们要逃命了
No, no, please, we have to go!
- 啊！ - 快跑
- Ahh!  - Run.
- 我们走  - 救命！
- Let's go!  - Help!
去拿零件
Go get the parts.
爸爸
Dad!
他们在追捕我们的儿子
They were after our boy.
为什么他们要抓走我们的孩子
Why would they want our boy?
好
Right.
- 去把水泵打开 动作快点  - 马上就去
- Turn on the water pumps. Quickly.  - Right away, sir.
- 不  - 我们想办法把他们救出来
- No!  - Let's try to get them out!
- 没事了 我会保护你们的  - 没事了
- Okay, I'll take care of you!  - All right.
可算找到你了 没事吧
There you are. All right?
跟我来
Come this way.
你救不了他的 罗兰
You couldn't save him, Roland.
长官 感应到灵力
Sir, Shine.
就是那个男孩 抓住他
That's the boy. Get him.
杰克
Jake.
- 他们是冲他来的  - 我知道
- They're here for him.  - I know.
罗兰
Roland.
- 你要干什么  - 别说话
- What are you doing?  - Quiet.
罗兰 快救救我 求求你
Roland. Please. Help me, please.
快走 赶快
Let's go! Let's go!
我们得赶紧离开这儿
We need to leave.
他在这里不安全
He's not safe here.
要是他不离开 你也会有生命危险
And as long as he's here, you aren't either.
我们来断后
We have this fight.
- 走吧  - 快
- Come on.  - Go.
杰克
Jake.
用灵力时要注意 他们会追踪你
Be careful using the Shine. They're tracking you.
传送门准备就绪
Portal alignment complete.
快
Come on.
不 还没熟呢
No, it's not ready yet.
- 他有刀子  - 他只是个厨子
- Knife.  - He's a chef.
走吧
Come on.
好多人啊
So many people.
你需要治疗 不能再耽误了
We need to get you help. Right now.
他们使用了通道
They had a portal.
他们溜走了
I think they're gone.
把坐标发给我
Get me the coordinates.
这是你们最后一次侥幸逃脱了 我的朋友
One last time around the wheel, old friend.
这太疯狂了
This is madness.
你不能揣着枪进医院的
You can't walk into a hospital here carrying guns.
相信我 来吧
Trust me. Come on.
我来负责交谈
Let me do all the talking.
你好 这里是劳丽 朗和杰克的家
Hi. You've reached Laurie, Lon and Jake.
请留下你的口信
Please leave a detailed message...
我们会尽快回复你
...and we'll get back to you as soon as possible.
真糟糕 试试看
This is awful. Try it.
- 这是啥啊 看着真恶心  - 是很糟心 但你还是得试试
- That looks gross. What is it?  - You got to try it. It's terrible.
- 糟心的话 我压根儿就不想试  - 好像是个芒果
- I don't want to try it if it's terrible.  - It's like mango...
现在这里的动物还能说话吗
Do the animals here still speak?
啥 不会 那只是个广告
What? No, that's a commercial.
等下 你说“还”是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean by "still"?
他在这儿
He's in here.
德斯钦先生
Mr. Deschain.
我们给你注射了抗生素
I see the antibiotics are kicking in.
按一到十的等级划分 你的疼痛属于几级
On a scale of one to 10, how bad is your pain?
好吧
Okay...
你的情况看上去很糟糕
You were in very bad shape.
你还能坐起身 我感到很意外
I'm surprised you're even sitting up.
我比大多数人都要强壮
I'm stronger than most.
看得出来
We get that sentiment a lot.
那么除了感染和在化装舞会事故中
So aside from your infection and the wound from the...
…受的伤外…
...costume-party incident...
我们还发现了甲型 乙型和戊型肝炎的迹象
...we also found traces of hepatitis A, B, E, and...
还有慢性辐射病
...chronic radiation sickness.
过去几个月中 你有出国旅游吗
Have you traveled overseas in the past couple of months?
没有 我一直都待在地球
No. I've been here on Keystone Earth.
那你们到底能不能治好我
So am I cured or not?
你得在医院呆一晚好让我们监测你的情况
We're going to keep you here for the night to monitor your progress.
也许明天下午 你干什么 不行
Maybe tomorrow afternoon-What are you doing? No.
- 我不能留在这儿  - 你得躺回病床上
- I can't stay here.  - You need to get back on that.
- 德斯钦先生 你得  - 谢谢你的检查
- Mr. Deschain, you need...  - For your services.
- 什么 等会儿  - 好人一生平安
- Wait, what?  - May your days be long.
但你得回到病床上
But you need to get back on that.
- 德斯钦先生  - 把我的枪带上
- Mr. Deschain?  - Bring my guns.
这是些止痛药和维他命
These are painkillers and vitamins.
你一次只用吃一到两
You only want to take one or two at a...
片 嘿 小可爱
...time. WOMAN: Hey, cutie.
能给我们也来点儿吗
Can we join the party?
我看你俩是三天不打 上房揭瓦
You have both forgotten the faces of your fathers.
我想你还是不要跟这里的人说话了
You probably shouldn't talk to people here.
这是啥
What is this?
糖
Sugar.
我们要怎么找到传送门 纽约可不是个小地方
How we gonna find the portal? New York's a pretty big place.
不知道
I don't know.
我也不能让沃特知道我是如何找到他的
I just can't let Walter know how I'm coming for him.
我有个主意
I've got an idea.
那些止痛药见效真快
These painkillers work fast.
好久都没感觉这么爽了
I haven't felt this good in years.
是啊 我们拿到宝了
Yeah, we got the good stuff.
那种糖还有吗
Got any more of that sugar?
在这里你不用害怕
There's nothing to be scared of.
我向你保证 不管发生什么
I promise you, whatever happens...
你都会安然无恙的
...you'll be at peace.
- 安然无恙  - 预言家所撒得谎
- You'll be...  - A seer who lies.
最为致命
The worst kind.
我开始喜欢你了
I like you already.
那么现在
Come now.
永别了
Good bye.
告诉我
Talk.
嘘
Shh.
不要反抗 他把那孩子带去哪儿了
Don't fight it. Where did he take the boy?
杰克
Jake?
杰克·钱伯斯 是的 他在哪儿
Chambers, yes. Where?
- 地…地…  - 地球
- Key... Key...  - Keystone Earth.
谢谢了
Thank you.
嘿 还记得我吗
Hey, remember me?
你提醒过我 说他们正在劫走儿童
You said they were crossing over kids.
你是他们中的一员吧
You were one of them, weren't you?
我丢失了灵力
I lost it. The Shine.
他们带你走的哪条路
Which way did they take you through?
- 不 不 你得赶紧逃跑  - 你还记得吗 哪个传送门 在哪里
- No, no, you have to run.  - Do you remember? A portal, a door.
- 任何线索都行  - 要结束了
- Anything, please.  - It's almost over.
一切都要结束了
It's almost over.
都要结束了 都要结束了
It's almost over. It's almost over.
听到了吗
Can you hear me?
记住 展示给我看看
Remember. Show me.
迪克西酒吧
Dixie.
杰克
Jake!
他们能追踪到灵力
They can track the Shine.
明白吗
Okay?
我知道你是谁
I know what you are.
枪侠
Gunslinger.
你走吧
Go.
线索应该足以让我们找到传送门了 只需回家再调查一下
Should have enough to find it. Got to get home and do some research.
- 回你家吗  - 是的 我得让妈妈知道我平安无事
- Your home?  - Yeah, I got to let my mom know I'm okay.
我们的追踪者遍布全城
We have trackers spread throughout the city.
目前尚未发现他们的行踪
There's no trace of him yet, sir.
已经尽其所能 但仍是心有余而力不足
Couple of small spikes, but not enough to hone in on.
别担心 伙计
Don't you worry, Dicky-boy.
- 我是来帮你们的  - 长官
- I've got you covered.  - Sir?
我给我们的朋友准备了个大惊喜 你随时待命
I left a surprise for our little friend. Just be ready.
- 你就在这儿等着吧  - 哥们儿
- You should probably wait here.  - Dude.
- 你最近跑哪儿去了  - 蒂米 呃
- Where the hell have you been?  - Timmy. Um...
这位是谁
Who's that?
我待会再告诉你
I'll tell you later.
妈妈和朗怎么样 他们肯定急疯了
How's Mom and Lon? They must be freaking out.
他们昨天就一直没回家
They haven't been home since yesterday.
妈妈 妈妈
Mom.Mom.
- 妈妈  - 杰克
- Mom?  - Jake.
- 妈妈 妈妈 妈妈  - 杰克
- Mom? Mom! Mom!  - Jake!
不
No.
不 不
No, no.
不 不 不
No, no. No, no, no.
No, no, no.
不要 妈妈 不
No, Mom. No, no, no.
不 不 妈妈
No, no, Mom.
不
No.
不 不 妈妈
No, no, Mom.
- 什么画  - 妈妈
- Drawings.  - Mom.
不会让你太痛苦的
I'll make it quick.
杰克
Jake!
不
No.
别这样 杰克
No, Jake.
- 别去看了  - 妈妈
- Don't see it.  - Mom.
这是他的圈套
It's what he wants.
- 他要追踪你  - 她去世了
- He's tracking you.  - She's dead.
别想那些
Close your mind.
别想那些 摒弃痛苦 杰克
Close your mind. Let the pain run through you, Jake.
他杀了她
He killed her.
- 我知道 我知道  - 他杀了她
- I know. I know.  - He killed her.
过来
Come here.
我会杀了他
I will kill him.
为我俩报仇
For both of us.
那黑暗塔怎么办
What about the Tower?
我妈妈也死了 你却一心只想着报仇
My mom died so you could have your revenge?
也许你的世界已经岌岌可危 但是我的世界还有希望
Maybe your world is almost gone, but mine isn't.
你说过的 只要黑暗仍未消散
You said it yourself, as long as the darkness is out there...
这座塔将一直处于危险之中
...the Tower's always in danger.
我觉得 他们说得对
You know, they were right.
你不是一个称职的枪侠
You're not a Gunslinger.
看这儿
Here.
这个通道入口在一个叫做迪格西皮格的酒吧里
It's called the Dixie Pig.
在普利茅斯和珍珠路的交界处
It's on Plymouth and Pearl.
我年轻的时候
When I was younger...
我会背诵枪侠的信条
...I would recite the Gunslinger's Creed.
它能使思绪平静下来
It calms the heart and the mind.
我已经很多年没背过了
I haven't spoken it for years.
枪准不在于双手
I do not aim with my hand.
违此者 忘祖也
He who aims with his hand has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于双眼
I aim with my eye.
枪准不在于双手
I do not shoot with my hand.
违此者 忘祖也
He who shoots with his hand has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于头脑
I shoot with my mind.
枪准不在于所用之枪
I do not kill with my gun.
违此者 忘祖也
BOTH He who kills with his gun has forgotten the face of his father.
枪侠不倒
Not while the Tower still stands.
塔就不倒
Not while you still stand.
- 枪准在于我的心  - 枪准在于我的心
- I kill with my heart.  - I kill with my heart.
很好
That's good.
你的灵力就是你的武器 杰克
Your Shine is your weapon, Jake.
枪是我的武器
Guns are mine.
有什么需要帮忙的么
Can I help you fellas?
- 嘿  - 四五口径子弹
- Hey.  - Forty-five-caliber bullets.
额
Uh...
- 我只有…  - 我们全部带走
- I only have...  - We'll take them all.
按他说的做 他不会伤害你的
Just do what he says. He won't hurt you.
我不想惹上什么麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
那好 你比大多数人都聪明的多
Well, then you're smarter than most.
快点
Hurry Up...
走吧 带你去个安全的地方
All right, let's get you somewhere safe.
枪侠
Gunslinger.
你想我了吗
Did you miss me?
我觉得 你肯定想我了
Well, I guess you did.
罗兰 罗兰 罗兰
Roland! Roland, Roland.
杰克 快跑
Jake, run.
快跑
Run!
我猜你找到了指南针的话 肯定还会来找我的
I see you finally found a compass, yet you still came to me.
因为我才是你唯一的，目标 罗兰
Because I'm your only destination, Roland.
开火
Fire away.
这不是我 我控制不住自己
It's not me. I'm not doing this.
首先 你想保住黑暗塔
First, you want to save the Tower.
然后 你想杀掉黑衣人
Then, kill the Man in Black.
你就像狗一样 反反复复的把扔出去的棍子叼回来
You are like a dog fetching a stick over and over.
你有没有告诉那个孩子老一代枪侠是怎么死的
You tell the kid what happened to the old crew?
你有没有告诉他 每个在你身边的人都死在了我的手里吗
You tell him that everyone that walks with you dies by my hand?
这次不会了
Not this time.
你的妈妈 皮肤软软的哟
Your soft-skinned mother?
- 还有你的枪侠朋友们  - 跟我当面对峙啊
- Your Gunslinger friends?  - Face me.
你在你那垂死的老父亲面前哭嚎着
Your whimpering excuse for a dad.
别天天摆弄你的魔法了 沃尔特 出来跟我当面对峙啊
Stop hiding behind your magic and face me, Walter!
我们都知道我们俩无论谁先死
We both know that no matter who crosses the finish line first...
宇宙终将消亡的
...the universe will die out eventually.
死亡才是胜者
Death always wins.
就是如此
That's the deal.
不 不
No, no.
罗兰
Roland.
耶
Yeah!
杰克·钱伯斯
Jake Chambers.
正如传言的那样 你这孩子天赋异禀啊
You are the full package, as advertised.
赛尔 做好准备
Sayre, get ready.
有个又高又黑又帅的家伙要来搞破坏
Tall, dark and handsome is about to crash the party.
我们走 快
Let's go, let's go! Move, move!
拿上枪就走
Take one and go.
好了 我们走 让所有人都脱离苦海 怎么样
Alrighty. Let's go put everyone out of their misery, shall we?
准备好了就启动 钱普
Any time, champ.
罗兰
Roland.
Roland...
他们要带我去那个地方
...they're taking me to that place.
小心点
Be careful.
坚持住
Hang on.
我来救你了
I'm coming for you.
我们会搞定他的 先生
We'll get him, sir.
拜拜
Bye.
祝你们末日愉快
Have a great apocalypse.
包围他
Close in on him!
好的
Okay...
- 开始吧  - 先生
- Let's go.  - Sir.
设备启动了
We're online!
- 是不是这一切终于要到来了  - 是的 是的
- It's really gonna happen, isn't it?  - Oh, yes, it is.
出了点毛病
Something's wrong.
出问题了 读数停滞了
Something's wrong here. The levels are plateauing.
- 可能是因为他…  - 在反抗
- It's as if he's...  - Fighting back.
你为什么要反抗
Why do you resist?
你的幻象不是指引你去找他 而是来找我
Your visions didn't bring you to him, they brought you to me.
他根本不喜欢你 他根本不关心你
He doesn't love you. He doesn't care for you.
实际上 他这段时间一直利用你来找我
In fact, he's been using you this entire time to get to me.
这就是你为什么在这儿 这是你的宿命
This is why you're here. This is your destiny.
你杀了我妈妈
You killed my mom!
是的 完美极了 开始了
Yes, that's it. There we go.
是入口 关了它
Portal. Close it.
- 关掉它  - 我关不了
- Close it!  - I can't!
等等
Wait.
我的天 是那个孩子干的
Oh, my God. It's the kid.
他让那个入口保持开启状态
It's the kid! He's keeping the portal open!
真是了不起啊
Ahh. Impressive.
老朋友 你这是一定要我亲自上阵啊
So you wanted me to face you, old friend?
我来了
Here I am.
刚好你和塔要同时倒下了
It's fitting that you and the Tower should fall together.
罗兰
Roland.
罗兰 快起来
Roland, get up.
枪准不在于双手
I do not aim with my hand.
违此者 忘祖也
He who aims with his hand has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于双眼
I aim with my eye.
枪准不在于双手
I do not shoot with my hand.
违此者
He who shoots with his hand...
忘祖也
Has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于头脑
I shoot with my mind.
枪准不在于所用之枪
I do not kill with my gun.
违此者
He who kills with his gun...
忘祖也
Has forgotten the face of his father.
枪准在于我的心
I kill with my heart.
妈妈 爸爸
Mom, Dad.
- 太好了  - 亲爱的
- There they are.  - Sweetheart.
太好了 你们没事
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
许多人目击了…
Multiple witnesses saw...
天空中出现的怪象
...the strange phenomena in the sky.
似乎我们看到了最坏的状况
Looks like we've seen the worst of it...
气象中心发布声明
The weather center has now  issued  a statement...
称这可能是某种非常强烈的太阳耀斑导致的
...that it may have been some kind of very intense solar flare.
- 给你  - 这是什么
- Here.  - What is this?
- 谢谢  - 谢谢 热狗
- Thank you.  - Thanks. Hot dog.
野蛮人
Savages.
什么品种的
What breed?
不 这没有什么品种
No, it's not a breed.
我得离开这了 杰克
I have to leave here, Jake.
你明白的 对吗
You understand that, don't you?
我明白
I know.
你干嘛不跟我一起
Why don't you come with me?
真的可以跟你一起么
Really?
你在这儿又没事干
You have nothing here.
而且 你还可以帮帮我
Besides, I could use your help.
额
Uh...
好的 好的
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
枪侠
Gunslinger.